http://bppcc.com/privacy/

Privacy Notice
BPP is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. BPP will process your personal data in accordance with the GDPR.
Our full Privacy Policy can be accessed here.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Cookies
This site uses cookies – small text files that are placed on your machine to help the site provide a better user experience. In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences, store information for things like shopping carts, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications like Google Analytics.
As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at the About Cookies website which offers guidance for all modern browsers.
Updates to this Privacy Notice
BPP Privacy Notice/Policy is reviewed on a regular basis and when legislation requires.  The Policy will be updated herewith accordingly.
[types field="bpp-sidebar-image" class="bpp_sbimg"][/types]
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.Ok
